Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee School of Information Studies Records, 1956-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
UW-Milwaukee School of Information Studies Records, 1956-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. School of Information Studies
UWM Archival Collection 23
Accession 2008-072
Accession 2011-041
Accession 2013-024
20.4 cubic ft. (30 boxes) 106 digital text files (6.68 MB) plus additions of 3.2 cubic ft. (5 boxes) and 2,116 digital files (174 MB)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Records of the school and its predecessors. Most of the collection documents the daily administration of the school such as curriculum development, staffing, funding, and organization changes. Records detailing the process of the school's accreditation by the American Library Association contain correspondence, reports, credentials, statistics, course syllabi, and on-site visit reports. The collection also contains unrestricted summaries of teaching evaluations. Other miscellaneous records document the school's commitment to the inner city user, affirmative action, committees of the school, and the student and alumni associations.
The Department of Library Science was made a department in the School of Education in 1956, with Donald Woods as chairperson. The Department of Library Science was transferred from the School of Education to the College of Letters & Science in 1965. The University of Wisconsin Board of Regents authorized the creation of the School of Library and Information Science on July 1, 1966. In the fall of 1966, the first graduate library science program began and the first library science degrees were granted in June 1967. From 1966 until 1970-the school offered two programs: Master of Arts in Library Science and Master of Science in Information Science. The information science degree was dropped in 1973 and the school was renamed the School of Library Science. The school received ALA accreditation in July 1976. In spring 1981, the program became the School of Library and Information Science. In February 1984, the school's master's degree was officially changed to Master of Library and Information Science. The school began offering a bachelor's degree in Information Studies in 1995. In 2001, the school changed its name once more, this time to the School of Information Studies. The School of Information Studies also began offering a Bachelor’s of Science and Information Resources in 1995.
Chairs, Directors, and Deans of the School and its Predecessors
1956-1961 Donald A. Woods (Department Chair)
1962-1965 Eloise Rue (Department Chair)
1965-1966 Rachel Schenk (Acting Director)
1966-1971 Frank Schick (Director)
1971-1974 Robert Little (Acting Director)
1974-1976 Doralyn Hickey (Director)
1976-1977 Doralyn Hickey (Dean)
1977-1979 Frederick Olson (Acting Dean)
1979-2002 Mohammed Aman (Dean)
2002-2005 Thomas A. Walker (Interim Dean)
2005-2010 Johannes Britz (Dean)
2010-2011 Hope A. Olson (Interim Dean)
2011-2012 Dietmar Wolfram (Interim Dean)
2012-2014 Wooseob Jeong (Interim Dean)
2014- Tomas A. Lipinski
Records of the dean of the school and its predecessors. Most of the collection documents the daily administration of the school such as curriculum development, staffing, funding, and organization changes. Records detailing the process of the school's accreditation by the American Library Association (ALA) contain correspondence, reports, credentials, statistics, course syllabi, and on-site visit reports. The collection also contains unrestricted summaries of teaching evaluations. Other miscellaneous records document the school's commitment to the inner city user, affirmative action, committees of the school, the student and alumni associations.
The collection consists of accreditation files that include material such as correspondence, credentials of the faculty, reports, statistics and other information gathered at the request of the ALA. Faculty memos detail plans for accreditation visits, personnel changes, and graduate school standards for library education. Correspondence between SOIS and the UWM administration is largely routine, providing updates on the accreditation process.
The dean's correspondence contains items that were sent between the dean and the SLIS faculty concerning funding, the curriculum, and the program in general. There is also some correspondence from students, administration, other library schools and libraries. There are also several folders containing information regarding the School's relocation in Bolton Hall.
The collection also contains records concerning the Association of American Library Schools, of which the UWM SOIS was a member. Included are meeting agendas and minutes, conference information, and other correspondence relevant to being a member school.
The memoranda document the daily activity of the school with memos between the faculty and staff, as well as with the university administration. The memoranda files also contain other documents, such as applications for study and grievance procedures.
Also included are self-studies which were conducted as part of the process of ALA accreditation, and the reports reveal much about the administrative structure, faculty, renaming, resources, and staff of the school.
Teaching evaluations list the professor/instructor, the name of the course, date, and the students' responses to the questionnaires. There is also some miscellaneous material about SOIS efforts to improve inner city library service; the SLIS student and alumni organizations; colloquia (speakers) the school sponsored; and minutes from the various committees. Several folders contain information pertaining to the Information Technology 2000 Computer Training Program (IT2000).
This collection was received in, and is organized in, multiple parts. Additional materials have not been physically or intellectually arranged and interfiled, and researchers may need to consult more than one part of the collection to locate similar materials.
UWM Archival Collection 23: Records, 1956-2014
The collection contains three additional accessions.
Accession 2008-072: Milwaukee Teachers Education Center materials, 1975-2002
Accession 2011-041: Additions, 1982-2012
Accession 2013-024: Subject, Personnel, and Accreditation Digital Files, 1990-2003
Finding aid for the personnel files in boxes 8-12 available in the Archives.
A spreadsheet with file-level information on the electronic records is available in the Archives department. The spreadsheet contains information on file title (where applicable), author, dates created, modified, and printed, file formats, number of pages, and software used to create the file. The files were inadvertently altered during transfer, so CreateDate and FileModifyDate fields may not include correct information. Additional technical metadata is available; consult an archivist for more information.
Related Material in the UWM Libraries
UW-Milwaukee Office of the Provost and Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs Records UWM Archival Collection 12
UW-Milwaukee School of Education Records UWM Archival Collection 5
Administrative/Restriction Information
Electronic files must be viewed on computers in the Archives. Contact an archivist for more information. The unclassified personnel files in boxes 8-12, the search and screen committee materials in box 1 of accession 2011-041, and the academic appeals files and search and screen committee files in box 2 of accession 2013-024 are restricted in accordance with UWM Personnel File Policy S-42. Access to the records is regulated by Section III. A.2 and III. A.3. The files in box 23 are restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA). See an Archivist for more information. There are no access restrictions on the rest of the collection, which is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
The school transferred the collection to the Archives prior to 1989. The School of Library and Information Science transferred additional accessions in 1999 and 2004. Accession 2008-057 was transferred in April 2009; accession 2008-072 in June 2009; accession 2009-006 in July 2009, and accession 2010-035 in January 2011. The School transferred additional materials to the Archives in April 2009 (accession 2008-057), June 2011 (accession 2010-063), May 2012 (accession 2011-041), and November 2013 (accession 2013-024).
As of May 23, 2013, all electronic files were accessible on a Intel Core 2 Duo CPU (2.33 GHz, 1.95 GB RAM) running Windows XP Professional Version 2002, with Service Pack 3. Software used to access the files includes Microsoft Office 2007, Firefox v. 21.0, and Adobe Reader XI.
The collection includes records in the following file formats:
Microsoft Word Document 97-2003 [.doc]
Microsoft Word for Windows 2007 onwards [.docx]
Hypertext Markup Language [.html]
Acrobat PDF 1.3-1.4 - Portable Document Format [.pdf]
Contents List
- Records, 1956-2014, UWM Archival Collection 23; 20.4 cubic ft. (30 boxes) 106 digital text files (6.68 MB)
  - "The Abstract", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Dean's Council Retreat Materials, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Academic Misconduct Officer, 2009-2010 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Academic Planning Committee, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Academic Planning, Steering Committee, 2002-2004 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Accreditation, 1984-2003 (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
  - Accreditation Questionnaire, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Accreditation Standards, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Acquisitions Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Information Science/Technology Entitlement, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Ad Hoc Executive Committee Meeting, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administration Reorganization Plans, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Staff Meetings, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Admission Scholastic and Appeals Committee, 2002-2004 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Restricted
  - Admissions and Awards Committee, 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid Committee
    - 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1984-1995 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1971-1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Council Meeting, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action, 1993-1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - African Americans in Education Conference, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - ALISE (Association for Library and Information Science Education)
    - 2000-2006 (Box 26, Folder 11-13)
    - Reports, 1997-2001 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association, Newsletter, 1969-1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Day Celebration, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Newsletters, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aman Communications
    - Correspondence, 1980-1989, 2000-2002 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Ecole do Bibliotheconomie et des Sciences de I'information [Universite de Montreal] COA Review, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - International, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Office, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 6-8)
      - Provost, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Council on Education, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Library Association, Accreditation, 1966-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10-40)
  - American Library Association Spectrum Initiative, Miscellaneous Communications, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - American Society of Information Science, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Annual Resource Report, Attachment 2, Web-based 901 Certification, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Articles and Speeches, Dean Aman's, 1979-1991 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
  - Association of American Library Schools, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 42-46)
  - Association of Research Libraries, 1972-1979 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Audit, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Bibliotheca Alexandrina
    - 1987-2005 (Box 26, Folder 14-16)
    - Architectural Brief and Competition Rules, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Collection Development Paper, 1990-2003 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Friends of, 1988-1990 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Bio of Dean, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Black and Gold Commission Final Report, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Bolton Hall Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Bolton Hall Fifth Floor Plan, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Bolton Move, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Brochures, 1977-1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - BSIR (Bachlor's of Science in Information Resources)
    - Marketing Materials, 2004-2009 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Name Change and Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Program Report/Program Accomplishments, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Proposal, 1996-2001 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Budget Communication and Report, 1993, 2005-2007 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Budget Planning Document for 1995-1996, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Budget Planning Document for 1996-1997, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Budget Planning Documents, 1990-1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Budget Planning Documents, 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Budget Planning Meeting, Preliminary Materials, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Budget Planning, Review, 2005-2007 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Bureau of Social Science Research, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Buzz Newsletter, 2004-2007 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Certification, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Clippings, 1987-2002 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Codification Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Colloquia
    - 1968-1982 (Box 1, Folder 52-54)
    - 1968-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
  - Combined Program in Information and Communication Sciences, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Commencements, 1970-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Accreditation
    - 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 6-9)
    - 5-Year Review, 1994-1998 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Accreditation Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Accreditation Report and Response, 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Active Narrative Material, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence
      - 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - 1996-2003 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence/Reports
      - 1972-1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - 1985-1996 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - 1986-2002 (Box 27, Folder 7-10)
    - Program Presentaion, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Reports
      - 1982-1987 (Box 27, Folder 12-14)
      - 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 15-16)
      - 1994 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Self-Study Follow-Ups, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Statistics, 1995-2003 (Box 27, Folder 19-20)
  - Committee on Conversion of the MALS to MLS, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Cooperation with Developing Universities, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1967-1974 (Box 2, Folder 12-14)
  - Community Programs, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Comprehensive Examination Committee, 1994-2002 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Computer Policy Committee, 2002-2007 (Box 19, Folder 13-14)
  - Conferences and Workshops, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
  - Coordinating Council for Higher Education, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17-24)
  - Correspondence
    - 1956-1982 (Box 2, Folder 25-47)
    - 1956-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1-5)
    - 1979-1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 1989-1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - 1994-2004 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Music Librarianship, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Council of Wisconsin Libraries (COWL), 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Culminating Event, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Curriculum Committee
    - 1967-1982 (Box 3, Folder 6-14)
    - 1983-1995 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 1995-2002 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Dean's Communications, 2003-2008 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Dean's Correspondence
    - Aman, Mohammed
      - 1999-2002 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - 2001-2005 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Walker, Thomas, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Dean's Meeting, 2009-2011 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Dean's Retreat, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Degree Proposals, 1998-2005 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Department of Public Instruction, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Distance Education Committee
    - 1991-2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Division of Urban Outreach, 1973-1980 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - Doctoral Committee, 1991-2002 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Dual MLIS and Anthropology or English Degrees, Correspondence, 1988-1997 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Entitlement Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - ERIC Proposals and Budget, 1966-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
  - Event Posters, 2002-2011 (Box 25)
  - Exchange Agreements with Other Institutions
    - Kenya, 1985-1988 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Middle East, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee
    - 1968-1983 (Box 3, Folder 20-26)
    - 1983-1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 1985-1995 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 1995-2002 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - 2002-2004 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Expansion on Campus, 1994-2001 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Faculty and Staff Meeting Minutes, 1965-1978 (Box 3, Folder 27-35)
  - Faculty as a Whole Curriculum Committee, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Faculty Council Meetings
    - 1990-1995 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
    - 2002-2006 (Box 19, Folder 18-21)
    - 2006 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 2007-2008 (Box 27, Folder 29-30)
    - Minutes
      - 1979-1989 (Box 3, Folder 36-39)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 31-32)
      - 2008-2010 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Five-Year Review of School of Library and Information Science
    - 1977 (Box 3, Folder 41-44)
    - 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Focused MLIS Degree in United Arab Emirates Proposal, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - GPR Investment Plan, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Curriculum Committee, 2002-2004 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Graduate Faculty Council Review of Master's Program, 1989, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Library Education for Wisconsin, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Graduate of the Last Decade (GOLD), 2003-2005 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Program, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Program Review of Master of Library and Information Science, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School Committee, 2003-2008 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School Review, 1989-2000 (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
  - Grievance Petition against Doralyn Hickey, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Guide to Study Student Handbook, 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - History, 1969-1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Vel Philips, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - IDAMS Agreement between SLIS and UNESCO, 1992-1994 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Information Resource Management Program, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Information Technology 2000 Computer Training Program
    - 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Budget Correspondence, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Career Planning Professional Student Handbook, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Conference, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Contract and Access Concerns, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Department of Labor Visit, Correspondence, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Extramural Support Report, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Millenium Information Technology and Careers
      - 2000-2003 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Companion Strategy, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Report to Helen Bader Foundation, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - University Partnership Funds and Helen Bader Foundation Grant Application, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Inner City Library Service Institute, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Inner City Newsletter, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Inner City Project, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Inside SOIS, 2009-2012 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Instructional Media, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Institute for Legal and Ethical Issues in the New Information Era: Challenges for Libraries, Museums, and Archives (ILEI), 2000 (Box 28, Folder 10-13)
  - Institute on Non-Book Materials, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
  - Institute on the Acquisition of Foreign Materials for U.S. Libraries, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 13-15)
  - Instituto Tecnologico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey Exchange
    - Articles, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Photographs, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Institutional Research, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Intellectual Property Liason, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - International Projects, 1978-1999 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Internship/Workshop Programs, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Leaders Forum Online Mentoring Project, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Leon H. Sullivan Conference, Miscellaneous Communications, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Library Automation, Research, and Consulting Association, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Library Council Event, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Library Manpower Study, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Little, Robert D., 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Masters in Archival Studies
    - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Entitlement, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Instructor Information, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Proposal and Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Masters in Information Resources Management, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Masters in Instructional Technology Correspondence, 1998-2003 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - May Hill Arbuthnot Honor Lecture, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 19-21)
  - Memoranda, 1966-1980 (Box 4, Folder 22-33)
  - Memorandums and Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 28, Folder 20-21)
  - Memorandums, Various, 1986, 2001-2003 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Midwest Regional Library Network Final Report, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Milwaukee Idea, 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Milwaukee Teacher Education Center Student Cohort Accommodation Agreement Communications, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Minnesota Libraries, Customized MLIS, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Misson and Goals, Drafts, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - MLIS Jointly Organized with Chinese University of Hong Kong, 1995? (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Move, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Multicultural Affairs Council, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Naming of School, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - National Center for Educational Statistics, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - National Library Systems, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Newspaper Clippings
    - 1977-2001 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Moscow, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - News Releases
    - 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - 1985, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 2000-2005 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - 2008-2014
      Records captured as part of UWM Web Collection.
  - Olson, Frederick I., Memoranda and Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Organization Chart, 1990-2012 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Outreach, 1987-2000 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Pamphlets and Flyers, 2005-2010, undated (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - PhD Newsletter, 2011-2012 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Placement and Salary Survey, UWM Report, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Planning Documents
    - 1981-1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 1986-1995, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Enrollment Programs, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Planning Groups, Communications, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Planned Parenthood Project, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Position Paper and Mergers, 1999-2003 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Position Paper on Distance Education Programs, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Pre-College Academy and Information Literacy, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Press Release
    - 2001-2003 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Resolution for Professor Emeritus Theodore Samore, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Proficiency, Comprehensive Exam Committee, 2002-2004 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Proficiency Requirement Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Program Array Review
    - 1969-1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - 1996-2000 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - 1997 (Box 4, Folder 41)